Privacy Policy
==============

##### PRIVACY POLICY

**  
Description of Users and Acceptance of Terms  
**This Privacy Policy applies to visitors to the Website, who view only publicly-available content (“Visitors”), and customers who have purchased a Subscription to our Services (“Customers”).

By visiting our Website, Visitors are agreeing to the terms of this Privacy Policy and the accompanying [Terms of Use](https://youtooz.com/pages/terms-of-use "Terms of Use"). By purchasing a Subscription, each Customer is agreeing to the terms of this Privacy Policy and the accompanying [Terms of Use](https://youtooz.com/pages/terms-of-use "Terms of Use").

Capitalized terms not defined in this Privacy Policy shall have the meaning set forth in our [Terms of Use](https://youtooz.com/pages/terms-of-use "Terms of Use").

**The Information We Collect and/or Receive  
**You authorize us to collect and/or receive such information.

1. Billing Information:   
    In order to purchase a Subscription to our Services, you will be required to provide certain information in addition to the Personal Information noted above. Such information may include a credit card number, expiration date, billing zipcode, activation code, and similar information (collectively, the “Billing Information). Such Billing Information will be collected and processed by our Third Party Payment Vendor pursuant to the terms and conditions of their privacy policies and terms of use, and we do not obtain access to any Billing Information.
2. Order Information
3. Third-Party Analytics:   
    We may use one or more third-party analytics services (such as Google Analytics) to evaluate your use of the Services, compile reports on activity, collect demographic data, analyze performance metrics, and collect and evaluate other information relating to the Services and mobile and Internet usage. These third parties use cookies and other technologies to help analyze and provide us the data. By accessing and using the Services, you consent to the processing of data about you by these analytics providers in the manner and for the purposes set out in this Privacy Policy. The third parties we currently work with are those listed below. These third parties may change from time to time, but in each case we will provide you with the links to view these organizations' privacy policies and find out more about what data they hold about you, what they do with it, and how to opt-out from certain data collection. Please be advised that if you opt out of any service, you may not be able to use the full functionality of the Website, and the Services.
4. The Information Collected by or Through Third-Party Advertising Companies. We may share, or we may permit third party online advertising networks, social media companies and other third party services, to collect, information about your use of our Website over time so that they may play or display ads on our Website, on other devices you may use, and on other websites, apps or services, including on Facebook. It is important to note, however, that we do not share any of your Personal Information with these parties. These third parties may use cookies, pixel tags (also called web beacons or clear gifs), and/or other technologies to collect this non-personal information for such purposes. Pixel tags enable us, and these third-party advertisers, to recognize a browser’s cookie when a browser visits the site on which the pixel tag is located in order to learn which advertisement brings a user to a given site. You may opt-out of the tailoring of advertising based on information we collect. To learn more about interest-based advertising and how you may be able to opt-out of some of this advertising, you may visit the Network Advertising Initiative’s online resources, at [http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices,](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices,) and/or the Digital Advertising Alliance’s resources atwww.aboutads.info/choices, and you may also adjust your ad preferences through your Facebook settings.  

**How We Use and Share Information  
**You authorize us to use the Personal Information, Wellness Information, Order Information and the Other Information (collectively, the “Information”) to provide and improve the Website and the Services; to solicit your feedback; and to inform you about our products and services and those of our promotional partners.  
You also authorize us to use and/or share Information as described below.

* Agents, Providers and Related Third Parties:   
    We may engage other companies and individuals to perform certain business-related functions on our behalf. Examples may include providing technical assistance, order fulfillment, customer service, and marketing assistance. These other companies will have access to the Information only as necessary to perform their functions and to the extent permitted by law. We may also share your Information with any of our parent companies, subsidiaries, or other companies under common control with us.
* Aggregated Information:   
    In an ongoing effort to better understand our Visitors, and Customers, we may analyze Personal Information with Other Information in anonymized and aggregate form in order to operate, maintain, manage, and improve the Website and the Services and for our own research purposes. This aggregate information does not identify you personally.
* Business Transfers:   
    As we develop our businesses, we might sell or buy businesses or assets. In the event of a corporate sale, merger, reorganization, sale of assets, dissolution, or similar event, the Information may be part of the transferred assets.
* Legal Requirements:   
    We may disclose your Information if required to do so by law, or in the good faith belief that such action or disclosure is necessary or appropriate to: (i) operate the Platform, (ii) comply with any legal obligation, report unlawful activity, cooperate with law enforcement, or protect against legal liability, (iii) protect and defend our rights, property, personnel, suppliers, sponsors, agents or licensors, or (iv) protect the personal safety of vendors, users of the Platform or the public.

We know how important it is to keep the Information you’ve entrusted to us confidential. We will not rent, sell or share your Information with third parties except as specifically approved or under the circumstances described above. If you do not want us to use or disclose Information collected about you in the ways identified in this policy, you should not use the Website or Services.

**How We Protect Your Information  
**We take commercially reasonable steps to protect the Information from loss, misuse, and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, or destruction. Please understand, however, that no security system is impenetrable. We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the Information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. However, we cannot guarantee the security of our databases, nor can we guarantee that the information you supply will not be intercepted while being transmitted to and from us over the Internet. In particular, e-mail sent to or from the Platform may not be secure, and you should therefore take special care in deciding what information you send to us via e-mail.

**Data Retention  
**We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. If you wish to cancel your account or request that we no longer use your information to provide you services contact us. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

* No items
    
* ∙
* $0.00 USD

Shopping Cart

Your cart is empty

Enable cookies to use the shopping cart
